A Guide to the Rockefeller University collection of The Medical Letter publication, 1996-2004 FA1103A
Rockefeller Archive Center
- TML, 45-65 - Immunization, Influenza, Flumist, 2003 August 18 (Box 87, Folder 1)
- TML, 45-21 - Montelukast (Singulair) for allergic rhinitis, 2003 March 17 (Box 87, Folder 2-4)
- TML, 45-3 - OTC Loratadine, 2003 January 6 (Box 87, Folder 5)
- TML, 45-41 - Insect repellents, 2003 May 26 (Box 87, Folder 6-8)
- TML, 45-81 - Rosuvastatin - a new lipid-lowering drug, 2003 October 13 (Box 87, Folder 9-12)
- TML, 45-35 - Insulin-sensitizing drugs for polycystic ovary syndrome, 2003 April 28 (Box 87, Folder 13-15)
- TML, 45-73 - Memantine for Alzheimer's disease, 2003 September 15 (Box 87, Folder 16-18)
- TML, 45-58 - Treatment of heat injury, 2003 July 21 (Box 88, Folder 1-2)
- TML, 45-90 - Atazanavir (Reyataz) and Emtricitabine (Emtriva) for HIV infection, 2003 November 10 (Box 88, Folder 3-6)
- TML, 45-88 - Aldurazyme (Laronidase), 2003 October 27 (Box 88, Folder 7-8)
- TML, 45-46 - Drug Interactions, 2003 June 9 (Box 88, Folder 9-12)
- TML, 45-85 - Lowering Plasma Homocystein, 2003 October 27 (Box 88, Folder 13-17)
- TML, 45-83 - Lp-Pla2 - A new marker of Vasular Risk, 2003 October 13 (Box 88, Folder 18-19)
- TML, 45-17 - Three new drugs for hyperlipidemia, 2003 March 3 (Box 88, Folder 20)
- TML, 45-17 - Three new drugs for hyperlipidemia, 2003 March 3 (Box 89, Folder 1-4)
- TML, 45-86 - Iodine-131 - Tositumomab (Bexxar) for treatment of Lymphoma, 2003 October 27 (Box 89, Folder 5-9)
- TML, 45-27 - Pneumococcal Conjugate Vaccine, 2003 March 31 (Box 89, Folder 10-11)
- TML, 45-78 - Influenza Prevention, 2003 September 29 (Box 89, Folder 12-14)
- TML, 45-19 - Peginterferon alfa (Pegasys) for Chronic Hepatitis C, 2003 March 3 (Box 89, Folder 15-16)
- TML, 45-55 - Pegvisomant (Somavert) for Acromegly, 2003 July 7 (Box 89, Folder 17-20)
- TML, 45-9 - Teriparatide for Osteoporosis, 2003 February 3 (Box 90, Folder 1-4)
- TML, 45-70 - Testim and Striant - two new testosterone products, 2003 September 1 (Box 90, Folder 5-8)
- TML, 45-1 - Smallpox vaccine, 2003 January 6 (Box 90, Folder 9-12)
- TML, 45-69 - Minimal surgery for treatment of GERD, 2003 September 1 (Box 90, Folder 13-16)
- TML, 45-23 - Drug-eluting Stents, 2003 March 17 (Box 90, Folder 17-19)
- TML, 45-23 - Drug-eluting Stents, 2003 March 17 (Box 91, Folder 1)
- TML, 45-61 - Omeprazole (Prilosec) (OTC), 2003 August 4 (Box 91, Folder 2-3)
- TML, 45-29 - Nitazoxanide (Alina) - a new anti-protozoal agent, 2003 April 14 (Box 91, Folder 4-5)
- TML - Drug of Choice for Cancer - Treatment Guidelines, 2003 March (Box 91, Folder 6-17)
- TML - Drug of Choice for Cancer - Treatment Guidelines, 2003 March (Box 92, Folder 1-4)
- TML - Weight Loss - Treatment Guidelines, 2003 December (Box 92, Folder 5-13)
- TML - Heart Failure - Treatment Guidelines, 2003 April (Box 92, Folder 14-18)
- TML - Drugs for rheumatoid arthritis - Treatment Guidelines, 2003 January (Box 93, Folder 1-7)
- TML - Drugs for Psychiatric Disorders, 2003 July (Box 93, Folder 8-18)
- TML - Rheumatoid Arthritis - Treatment Guidelines - Reprints, 2003 January (Box 93, Folder 19)
- TML - Rheumatoid Arthritis - Treatment Guidelines - Reprints, 2003 January (Box 94, Folder 1-4)
- TML - Assisted Reproduction - Treatment Guidelines, 2003 October (Box 94, Folder 5-13)
- TML - Drugs for Hypertension - Treatment Guidelines, 2003 February (Box 94, Folder 14-17)
- TML - Tobacco Addiction - Treatment Guidelines, 2003 March (Box 94, Folder 18)
- TML - Tobacco Addiction - Treatment Guidelines, 2003 March (Box 95, Folder 1-8)
- TML - Drugs for Epilepsy - Treatment Guidelines, 2003 May (Box 95, Folder 9-14)
- TML - Drugs for Lipid Disorders - Treatment Guidelines, 2003 August (Box 95, Folder 15-18)
- TML, 49-53 - SSRIs Safe for Children, 2003 July 7 (Box 95, Folder 19)
- TML, 49-53 - SSRIs Safe for Children, 2003 July 7 (Box 96, Folder 1)
- TML, 45-93 - Which SSRI, 2003 November 24 (Box 96, Folder 2-5)
- TML - Drugs for Allergic Disorders - Treatment Guidelines, 2003 November (Box 96, Folder 6-9)
- TML - Drugs for Pneumonia - Treatment Guidelines, 2003 September (Box 96, Folder 10-17)
- TML - Antimicrobial Prophylaxis for Surgery - Treatment Guidelines, 2004 (Box 97, Folder 1-10)
  Restricted material - Open in 2030
- TML - Drugs for Cardiac Arrhythmias - Treatment Guidelines, 2004 (Box 97, Folder 11-18)
- TML - Advice for Travelers - Treatment Guidelines, 2004 (Box 98, Folder 1-9)
- TML - Drugs for Migraine - Treatment Guidelines, 2004 (Box 98, Folder 10-15)
- TML - Tuberculosis - Treatment Guidelines, 2004 December (Box 98, Folder 16)
- TML - Tuberculosis - Treatment Guidelines, 2004 December (Box 99, Folder 1-5)
- TML - Drugs for Sexually transmitted infections - Treatment Guidelines, 2004 October (Box 99, Folder 6-12)
- TML - Drugs for Parkinson's disease - Treatment Guidelines, 2004 June (Box 99, Folder 13-18)
- TML - Drugs for Parkinson's disease - Treatment Guidelines, 2004 June (Box 100, Folder 1-3)
- TML, 46-22 - Abarelix (Plenaxis) for advanced prostrate cancer, 2004 March 15 (Box 100, Folder 4-5)
- TML, 46-9 - Daptomycin (Cubicin) for skin and soft tissue infections, 2004 February 2 (Box 100, Folder 6-8)
- TML, 46-10 - Emergency Contraception OTC, 2004 February 2 (Box 100, Folder 9-10)
- TML, 46-5 - Lasik and its alternatives - an update, 2004 January 19 (Box 100, Folder 11-14)
- TML, 46-15 - Effexor vs. SSRI, 2004 February 16 (Box 100, Folder 15-18)
- TML, 46-15 - Effexor vs. SSRI, 2004 February 16 (Box 101, Folder 1)
- TML - Choice of Antibacterial Drugs - Treatment Guidelines, 2004 March (Box 101, Folder 2-8)
- TML - Drugs for Peptic Ulcers - Treatment Guidelines, 2004 February (Box 101, Folder 9-17)
- TML - Drugs for HIV Infection - Treatment Guidelines, 2004 January (Box 101, Folder 18-19)
- TML - Drugs for HIV Infection - Treatment Guidelines, 2004 January (Box 102, Folder 1-4)
- TML - Drugs for Pain - Treatment Guidelines, 2004 July (Box 102, Folder 5-14)